RECRUITING SERVANTS FOR SONGRIM
That is not a letter.
What is there to a letter?
As long as it delivers your feelings.
You must have pitied me
for trying to get in here
as a servant.
You used to be
an incredibly experienced master.
I did feel bad for you.
I guess I helped you learn
about loyalty and duties.
Seeing how far you would go as my master,
I did think that I should do my best.
You must have felt pressured.
Not really. But I was in a dilemma.
I did not know if I should reply
as your young master or pupil.
Or just reply based on what I read.
What did you read?
Then should I also reply
based on what I read?
Also? What do you mean?
It is written here.
I will go this far just to see you.
"I can do anything
if it means being able to see you."
And this is my reply.
I also missed you.
That is my reply.
I will pretend like I did not hear that.
You should forget about the letter too.
You cannot get rid of something
that has already been exchanged.
It is as good as gone.
Once it burns away,
there will be nothing left.
So you think burning it
will make it disappear?
But know this, Master.
Your pupil
has recently learned to read
what cannot be seen.
I told you that I read Words of the Heart.
Do you want to check?
You must focus
when you are trying to read
what you cannot see.
And then…
call out the name of the receiver.
Mu-deok.
This is a clear and dangerous signal.
I am in love with this man.
There. I read you.
Some things are hard to see
because they are hidden,
not because they do not exist.
Just as you saw my blue mark
and found out I was a soul shifter,
you have once again caught me.
You have found another weakness of mine.
If you must call that a weakness,
then it is my weakness too.
You sent me a letter,
and I sent you a reply.
So we both share that weakness.
I guess I would not mind
having you share a weakness.
Honestly, I felt anxious
while we were apart.
You finally had what you always wanted,
and I had no power to do anything
even if you chose to betray me.
I even thought to myself that
I should have poisoned you
and found something to blackmail you with.
But Uk,
it seems you have
already poisoned yourself.
Poison?
You will become weak and miserable.
It is a terrible poison you cannot escape,
as its only antidote is
the person it is from.
Are you saying
the reason I missed you so much
was that I was poisoned?
Yes.
You were cruelly poisoned
by a dangerous assassin.
Think of it as that.
And it is not far from the truth.
So I was poisoned?
Then again, I did find it bizarre
that the person I missed
was you of all people.
You always threaten to kill me.
You even once threw a knife at me.
You mocked my incompetence
and even made my arm rot.
Yet you had the audacity to lie.
You were always so horrible to me,
but I could not get you out of my head.
I miss you first thing in the morning,
all throughout the day,
and even when I lie down to go to sleep.
- Stop.
- Why should I stop?
I confessed my feelings,
and you ruined it with poison.
So you should at least know my symptoms.
You said you were my antidote.
All I did was sincerely tell you
that I missed you, you wicked assassin.
You called it poison.
So from now on,
I will complain to you about my symptoms.
After all, I was poisoned.
I have nothing to be embarrassed about.
You called yourself an antidote,
so you deal with this toxin.
This young master is
the nephew of Songrim's leader
and the future leader of our organization.
I have come to greet you
on behalf of the leader.
Congratulations on
becoming a Songrim member.
Welcome.
You all did a great job today.
Tonight, you will be served
a generous amount of alcohol and meat.
So relax and have fun.
Go get yourselves a drink.
- Follow me.
- Yes, sir.
Young Master.
Are you acquainted with Mu-deok,
the servant who passed the exam today?
I am talking about the maid
who came in last.
ONE HUNDRED TWENTY-FIVE
SONGRIM SERVANT CONTEST
Number 125, Mu-deok.
You have passed!
Yes, I am very well-acquainted
with Mu-deok.
She fainted due to exhaustion
and got taken to Sejukwon.
I need to return
the bag she brought to the contest
along with this entrance plaque.
Is she still at Sejukwon?
Give it to me. I will give it to her.
You did great today.
All right. Let us go.
Mu-deok.
The reason you get lost
when you have a lot on your mind
is that you are focused
on too many things.
When that happens,
just try to focus on one thing.
So the only one in your mind
has been Jang Uk, Naksu.
Hey, Yul.
I happened to look inside Mu-deok's bag,
and I found something strange in here.
Is this not the whistle
you used to carry around?
The one you left at Danhyanggok.
Yes, that is mine.
Then why does Mu-deok have it?
Have you seen Young Master Park?
He apparently has my bag
and entrance plaque.
He gave them to me.
I see.
I will take that.
I left this at Danhyanggok.
Is that where you got this?
Yes.
I kept it because…
Because you are in love with me.
You told me that you were in love with me.
That is enough of an explanation.
I will just take my things.
You can keep the whistle.
I already told Dang-gu
that I gave it to you.
So I cannot take it back.
Why are you giving this to me?
You did not believe me
when I said I was in love with you.
Then do a better job
and make me believe it.
Up until now, I was just teasing them.
But Mu-deok is actually in love with Yul.
And seeing how Yul gave her that,
I am guessing
he has some feelings as well.
She probably asked him for the whistle.
When she needs something,
she easily flatters people and lies.
Yul even knew about Mu-deok's test.
He solved all the test questions for her.
She probably asked Yul
to help her out beforehand
because she was so desperate to pass.
She always gets what she wants.
Most importantly,
I saw them
affectionately spending time together.
What?
Affectionately?
Mu-deok and Yul met up
with each other separately.
I guess you did not know because you were
locked up in the Training Center.
Gosh.
No, I had no idea.
What if it is true?
I also missed you.
That is my reply.
She turned me down
because she did not like me.
She did not miss me like I did.
I was the only one who felt that way.
I…
I should just poison myself and die.
This is so embarrassing.
I am indeed in love with you.
I can tell you that
hundreds and thousands of times.
I do not know much about love,
but when you truly love someone,
you will not need to say it that often.
Because it will be hard
just to say it once.
That whistle used to belong
to a friend I once failed
to confess my feelings for.
I liked you a lot.
I have always wanted to tell her that.
I would also like to try.
Can I have that?
We will be seeing each other often
now that you are back in Songrim.
You may come to me if you need any help.
Thank you.
Uk managed to read Words of the Heart.
Master, you helped him, did you not?
I figured you might want to know,
so I came to inform you.
Tell Jin to take that book
and hand it over to Jinyowon.
There is a bone here.
Why?
Uk got angry at the fact that
everyone was reading it.
I think Master Seo Gyeong
would have felt the same way.
It seems like you are very fond of Uk.
He is a special young man,
so I have my eyes on him.
He is a clever fellow,
but Jin just wants to keep him locked up.
Are you sure
the ice stone is not somewhere in Songrim?
What makes you think that?
Twenty years ago,
Gwanju Jang Gang
performed the alchemy of souls.
Because of that,
a child that
should not have been born was born.
And that night,
the King's Star was in the night sky.
Is that child Jang Uk?
Yes.
A mage at Songrim unsealed the ice stone
and birthed the king's son
through the alchemy of souls.
And Jin Mu at Cheonbugwan knows this fact.
If the ice stone has
already fallen into their hands,
what kind of justification
can Songrim use…
to take that stone from them?
Jin has no choice but to hide Uk
because he wishes to protect Songrim.
Why?
Is there something I do not know about?
You little…
How am I supposed to say anything
to such a careless and imprudent punk?
How could you…
I hope I can wash this off.
He…
He is angrier than he was
when I told him I decided
to stop training with chaste herbs.
Wait. He got that scarf
from Maidservant Kim.
I am sorry.
We must finish cleaning
before the mages begin their day,
so move quickly.
- Yes, ma'am.
Where is Young Master Jang?
- Is he not here?
- Well…
I went to wake him up,
but he told me
he did not sleep a wink last night.
So he did not wake up? On his first day?
See you later, Mu-deok.
Young Master.
You must wake up.
Young Master!
Get up.
Or else I will beat you.
Wake up!
Stop being annoying and go.
I am going to sleep.
Are you out of your mind?
Do you have a death wish?
Yes, I would rather die.
What is the matter with you?
This is just a symptom.
I have been poisoned.
Uk, stop being stubborn with your spite.
I told you I was your antidote.
Here.
Here is your antidote.
I am sorry.
Hey, Uk.
I heard you read Words of the Heart.
I am impressed.
It is nothing to be impressed about.
I see you are reading about
the Hyeongong Technique.
I mastered that swordsmanship
when I was little.
If you teach me how to read
Words of the Heart,
I will teach you the Hyeongong Technique.
I am not sure.
Do it. Tell him you will do it.
Listen. I am a bit tired.
You can ask Master Lee
how to read Words of the Heart.
Uk.
I mastered Ryusu
around the same time you did.
So what do you say we fight a duel?
Then I will lend you
a precious sapphire mat
that I use for training.
If you train with that,
it will double your energy.
A sapphire mat?
That is very hard to come by.
Young Master, this is great.
But sapphire mats are really cold,
are they not?
I easily get cold these days.
So I do not need something like that.
What are you doing?
I have not been sleeping well these days,
so I am going to take a nap.
You missed your chance
to learn the Hyeongong Technique.
Are you mad?
The same goes for yesterday.
Sapphire mats are so rare,
but you refused, saying it was cold.
You should have said yes
even if you were to die on that mat.
You are unbelievable.
"You are mad. Just die."
That is all you ever say to me.
Just give me that.
What are you doing?
There is no space to nap together.
You must get through me to take a nap.
Move.
Make me.
It will not take too much effort.
Damn it.
I told you I missed you,
but you told me I was poisoned.
I need to sleep to recover from the shock,
so stop pushing me
and stay away for a bit.
You just want to make me feel frustrated.
Like I said, if I die, you die.
I am in agony,
so you should at least feel irritated.
I even have convulsions
when I sleep these days.
For how long, then?
I do not know.
Why? Does it frustrate you?
That will help me sleep well.
Young Master Jang will not stop sleeping.
You should beat him up and make him train.
The mages of Jeongjingak train
on their own accord.
How fast one masters one's energy
all depends on the individual.
I will not interfere
as long as he sticks to the rules.
But…
Do not worry. There he is.
Hello.
My head hurts so much.
I would like to go home
and recuperate by taking a bath.
Why does your head hurt?
You have not done a thing.
You cannot go home on your own accord.
That is against the rules.
Is it not?
Uk is an exception.
The leader gave him permission.
Why only him?
You may have been too busy
having fun to know about this,
but I made a deal with the leader
while I was locked in here.
I will be back.
I will go with him.
If you go, you will be fired.
You went through a lot to get hired.
Are you okay with getting fired?
Damn it.
Jang Uk went home.
Are you sure that is okay?
Let him do whatever he wants
so he can remain lazy.
My lord.
Lady Jin is asking you
to wait a little longer.
Is she with another guest?
I saw a servant from Cheonbugwan
on our way inside.
By any chance, do you think
Assistant Gwanju Jin Mu is here?
They are not close enough
to personally meet up like this.
Just in case, go see if anyone leaves.
If that is what Master Lee wants,
we will store Words of the Heart
safely in Jinyowon.
Were you meeting someone else before me?
A distant relative.
Is Young Lady Jin going to be
the official heir of Jinyowon?
That has not been decided yet.
My eldest daughter might still be alive.
It has been ten years since the accident.
Although she could not see,
she could feel energy
and could control relics like no other.
She was a very clever girl.
Unlike other babies,
it took her 13 months
to come out into this world.
She was born on the very day
that Gwanju Jang Gang picked
as a blessed day from the skies.
She was born exactly on the day
that Jang Gang picked for you?
Is it possible
to choose the date and time
of a baby's birth?
It just happened to match.
I would like to invite Master Lee
to Jinyowon someday.
Please tell him that.
I will.
I had her inside me for 13 months.
I cannot let her go like this.
I heard the ice stone has the power
to bring back the souls of the dead.
Gwanju.
Please help me.
I went far and beyond to protect my baby.
I will find you.
I will do everything I can
to find you.
- Did you check who the previous guest was?
- Yes.
It was Assistant Gwanju Jin Mu.
Since when did the leader of Jinyowon
acknowledge him as a family member
and meet with him like this?
He quietly left through the back gate.
They must have made a secret deal.
I wonder what that cunning man, Jin Mu,
is using as bait
to freely enter Jinyowon like this.
There is no way to find out where you are
since you cannot see.
If you do as you are told
and stay completely silent,
your life will be spared.
Do not make any noise.
Stand up.
Sit down.
Leave that one here. The others can go.
They are looking for the girl
in the portrait.
She must be blind.
He just said the others could leave,
but why is there no movement?
You can see.
What a pity.
I thought I had found an adequate girl.
Kill her.
I can do it!
I can be the girl in the portrait.
Please have mercy.
You said I was adequate.
If you need me to be blind…
then blind I will be.
You are a very daring girl. Stand up.
So you can act like you are blind?
I already am blind.
Let me see if that is true.
It really looks like
I have found an adequate girl.
You will do.
From now on, you are Jin Bu-yeon,
the missing daughter of Jinyowon.
Yes.
I am Jin Bu-yeon.
Uk has stopped once again.
What kind of cliff
do I have to push him off of this time?
I see you are working hard thanks to me.
Yes.
Thanks to you,
I will have to sweep the yard again.
Are you complaining?
Then I will have you gone.
You cheated your way in here.
If I say a word about this,
you will be fired.
Forgive me, Your Royal Highness.
I am grateful for the leaves
you have sprinkled for me to sweep.
You may keep going your way,
Your Royal Highness.
You should be grateful
for the answer sheet I gave you,
not these leaves.
I see you were not being grouchy.
You just wanted to receive credit.
Goodness, I was too slow to notice that.
I am grateful, Your Royal Highness.
Of course, you are grateful.
I solved those questions myself.
Do you even know
how to wash off ink stains?
You solved that question,
Your Royal Highness?
Yes, that is right. I am the Crown Prince.
Yet I learned that rice paste
gets rid of ink stains.
I even tried it myself,
and it actually worked.
Unbelievable.
I am forever indebted to you.
So tell me.
Are you happy to be with your master?
I heard Uk read Words of the Heart.
Yes.
He was the fastest mage
in Jeongjingak to have read it.
I doubt he read it with his skills.
He probably got lucky again.
But still, he beat you in a duel.
Goodness.
I know Uk's level of capacity very well
since I have fought against him.
He has bad swordsmanship,
and his spells are weak.
He got lucky and beat me by using Tansu.
It was not because he was skilled.
He is accurate.
That is why he came to Jeongjingak.
To become a mage of a higher level.
To be frank, he does not even have
what it takes to enter Jeongjingak.
If he manages to beat anyone here,
then I shall acknowledge him.
Using the Crown Prince
would not be such a bad idea.
Your Royal Highness.
Then how about we make a bet?
A bet?
What will I gain
from making a bet with you?
I will bet the most precious thing I own.
I will choose first.
I pick red. You can have the blue one.
Wait there. I will go to you soon.
I also missed you.
That is my reply.
- Young Master.
- Hey.
I brought honey biscuits, your favorite.
Are you also staying for dinner?
No, I am staying here for a few days.
- Is that allowed?
- The leader gave me his permission.
He let me be an exception for everything.
Well, I get why.
It only took you a few days
to read Words of the Heart.
It is absurd to make you abide
by the same rules as ordinary mages.
Are you happy about my achievements?
I am more than happy.
You have no idea how proud I am.
Maidservant Kim.
I know I have always disappointed you,
but you can feel proud now.
Should I get you a nice dress
to help you boast?
My goodness.
I do not wish for anything anymore.
I already feel like I have everything.
These days, people come up to me
and tell me that
you truly are your father's son.
They do?
Your father used to be called a genius,
and they say you are
as talented as your father.
People used to say I was nothing like him.
As you continue to achieve things,
there will be fewer people
who say that about you.
What if I do not do well?
Will they say I am not his son again?
No, that is not…
Tell them to go ahead
and say what they want about me.
I do not care anymore.
Yes, we should not
let that bother us anymore.
Frankly speaking, you are responsible
for your own achievements.
Your father is irrelevant.
He was never around for you anyway.
And to be honest, it is all because
I raised you well.
You will always be
my precious young master
no matter how competent
or incompetent you are.
Really?
Then can I go back
to slacking off like I used to?
Yes, if that is what you want.
But I thought you hated that.
Compared to the times
when you used to slack off at home,
you looked a lot happier
when you had just come back
from your training in Danhyanggok.
That is why I could not stop you
even though it seemed dangerous.
You see,
I want you to achieve
everything you want to achieve.
All right.
I should go back.
You are leaving?
Yes. If you forced me to leave,
then I would have refused to go.
But after that speech,
I should go and study.
I should do everything I can
to make you proud, Maidservant Kim.
How is your headache? Is it better?
Yes.
Horses and people are trained
through the carrot-and-stick approach.
But recently,
I kept getting hit by a stick.
Who in the world dared to hit you?
Do not worry. I am not one
to stay still after getting beaten.
Just pack me some snacks.
A ton of honey biscuits.
- This is going to be fun.
- Are you sure?
Hey, Uk.
You are finally here.
Yes.
Why does it seem like
you have all been waiting for me?
Are you fans of the honey biscuits
I bring from home?
You should go to the Training Center.
It will be fun.
- You have been waiting for me?
- Yes.
I will be your first opponent.
What?
Let us fight a duel.
If you refuse, you lose.
What are you talking about?
Just take it.
Uk has lost.
Gu Hyo, the winner,
may take the first gold toad.
What is going on?
I have made a bet.
I never made a bet with you,
Your Royal Highness.
Not with you. I have made a bet
with your maid, Mu-deok.
I told her that you did not
have the skills to beat any of the mages
here at Jeongjingak.
But your maid insisted that
you could at least beat one.
Mu-deok said that, did she?
You will fight a duel every day
for ten days.
If you fail to beat a single fight,
she will give me an item
that is most valuable to her.
Valuable?
What valuable item do you have?
It is something you gave me.
This is what she bet.
This jade looks very valuable,
so I want it for myself.
So I brought gold toads
as prizes for the match.
If you fail to beat a single opponent
before all those toads disappear,
this will be mine.
I am not interested
in taking part in this bet.
This is not a bet between us.
It is a bet I made with her.
If you give up,
you will not have won a single match,
so she will lose.
And this will be mine.
Young Master Jang.
That is the most precious object
I have ever received.
Please do your best
so you can win it back.
Look at that.
You really won this gold toad.
Of course. Uk may have managed
to read Words of the Heart,
- but he is a bad swordsman.
- What is going on?
The Crown Prince and Mu-deok
made a bet over Uk.
The Crown Prince brought gold toads,
so everyone is eager to participate.
The strongest mages
are lining up to fight Uk.
Put it down.
The Crown Prince mocked your competence.
As your master, I could not let it slide.
Do not lie to me. I know you.
I have been lazy these past few days,
so you made that senseless bet
to force me to train.
Yes, I did.
You will have to fight ten mages
regardless of your will.
The first duel was
incredibly disappointing.
Your sword was slow,
and your feet were heavy.
- Tomorrow's opponent is from the Jung--
- I am not doing it.
Even if you lose,
you always memorize what you see,
so it will help you learn.
- I told you I am not fighting.
- As you fight ten mages,
you will learn ten different spells.
- Mu-deok--
- Young Master.
Feel free to go home
for a bath again tomorrow.
Then you will never get that jade back.
All right, fine.
So you made this bet.
But…
But how could you bet on that?
You know why.
That was the only thing
to motivate you to fight hard and win.
When I said I missed you,
is this what you meant
when you said you had my weakness?
Yes.
You probably despise me right now,
but you cannot lose
what we share to someone else.
So this is why you said I was poisoned.
If you get it back,
I will give you a bright smile.
Just like an antidote.
Uk.
Return it to me no matter what.
It is the most precious item
I have ever received
in my entire life.
Is it really precious to you?
Do you not want it back
merely because of its price?
I will get it back from the Crown Prince.
It would be funny to share
that jade with him.
But it was not worth
sharing it with you either.
I heard you have been
visiting Sejukwon pretty often.
Is it because you wish
to appoint Master Heo as your master
and learn spells from him?
Do not be ridiculous.
You are my master.
I am only going there for treatment.
It allows me to get some fresh air.
Not to mention, fun things happen there.
You must enjoy hanging out
with the mages of Songrim.
I get to meet Yul, my cousin.
Park Dang-gu is
a lively person to be around.
As for Jang Uk, I would like
to teach him a lesson, but it is not easy.
He seemed elated
after having read Words of the Heart,
so I put him back in his place today.
He lost to a mage who just mastered Ryusu.
So people know his true competence now.
People no longer admire him.
That is a nice jade.
I got it in exchange for ten gold toads.
- Is it something valuable?
- That blue jade holds yin energy.
Where is the other one?
The other one?
Items with opposite energies
come in pairs.
There should be a red jade
that goes with it.
They are only valuable
when they are together.
So this is supposed to be a pair?
Eunuch Oh.
What does it mean when two people
share something that should be a pair?
It means they are married or a couple.
Damn it.
Do you not like the jade,
Your Royal Highness?
I do not like it. It gets on my nerves.
It extremely bothers me.
Take it away and smash it to pieces.
You cannot do that yet.
Jang Uk might win it back.
If he takes it back,
they will become a pair again.
Damn it.
- Master Lee.
- Yes…
What brings you here?
I wore hemp fabric all year round,
yet I never felt cold.
But…
after I wore this scarf,
I realized how cold it had been.
What is that over there?
What…
My goodness.
I never once thought flowers were pretty,
but I saw these flowers
and wanted to show them to you.
How pretty.
Are they for me?
These books…
You have nice books here.
What a great read.
About Maidservant Kim…
Is she sick?
I have not seen her at Songrim these days.
She went there yesterday.
She goes there often
to meet Young Master Jang.
I see.
She just did not drop by to see me.
She is with a guest right now.
A guest? Who is it?
I do not know who he is,
but he was a young man.
A young man?
From what I know, Maidservant Kim
is not acquainted with any young men.
Maidservant Kim.
Hello.
What are those weeds?
They are flowers.
- How could you call them weeds?
- Maidservant Kim.
Did you get upset that day
because I was a bit harsh?
Is that why you stopped visiting?
I really had no idea.
I thought you were sick.
I came here worried for nothing.
You should not have come.
You said you would never visit again.
When did I ever say that?
You are mistaken.
But still,
I am glad that you are all right.
If you were worried that I might be sick,
you could have brought me
a bundle of weeds like this one.
Do you need weeds?
I will get them for you.
I do not need them.
What I want from you are flowers,
not weeds.
I want you to show me
how much you care
by giving me something beautiful.
We still have a guest here,
so you should go.
Maidservant Kim.
Well…
Next time you come to Songrim to visit Uk,
I hope you will drop by and visit me too.
Wait…
Is she kicking me out
because I came empty-handed?
Maidservant Kim.
What a cold-hearted woman.
Seeing that his shoes
are smaller than mine,
he must be shorter than I am.
Do you like sweet snacks?
Yes, I do.
It is delicious.
Then here is one more…
For me.
- How do I look?
- You look pretty.
- Try this.
- Me?
How do I look?
- It should go there.
- I see.
Look. There is a flower shop over there.
You said you needed to buy flowers.
I need to buy flowers
to decorate Bu-yeon's room.
We might really find her this time.
Really? Will Jin Mu find her?
It is still a secret.
I really hope Bu-yeon comes back.
Then you will not be able to become
the leader of Jinyowon.
Instead, I will be free
to marry the man I want to marry.
I will be allowed to marry the man I love.
That is good news.
Then we should hurry up
and end our fake engagement.
Thank you for pretending
to be my fake betrothed.
I never pretended.
My feelings
were sincere.
But you are an heir to Songrim.
How could you think of marrying me
and moving in with my family?
I know.
I guess I was worried for nothing.
I was even getting ready
to get kicked out of the family.
Are you serious?
You were willing to give up on
becoming Songrim's heir because of me?
You said you did not want
a loveless marriage.
I figured if I married you,
you would at least marry
a man that loved you.
That is why.
Anyway, you should meet a man
that you have feelings for.
I feel like I have…
already met him.
If you hold onto me like this…
I will never give up on you.
My feelings for you are too strong.
There is no turning back.
I should get you flowers
to properly propose to you.
Let us go.
Send these flowers to the Jang family.
Did someone die in the family?
Why are you sending them
white chrysanthemums?
I almost made a huge mistake.
Right.
Everything from here
to all the way over there.
Send them all.
- All these flowers?
- Yes, send them all.
- I am sure she will like at least one.
- Goodness.
My goodness, thank you so much.
- Which one would you like?
- This one.
I can get you everything if you want.
You are the heir of Songrim.
Why would you court
the future leader of Jinyowon?
What was your plan?
Did you plan to give up your succession
and marry into their family?
Uncle, we are in love with each other.
Up until recently, Young Lady Jin
had feelings for Uk.
That is wrong. She proved it to me today.
Young Lady Jin said she could give up
becoming the leader of Jinyowon for love.
They only have one daughter.
Who will lead Jinyowon then?
That position is supposed to go
to the eldest daughter.
They are receiving help from Cheonbugwan
to help find her missing sister.
What?
Assistant Gwanju Jin Mu
visits them every day for that.
Jin Mu?
I too wish I had another brother
who could take over for me
and become Songrim's heir instead.
This is just a question out of curiosity.
Uncle, is there no chance
that you might have a secret child?
No one?
Not once?
Get out.
I said, get out.
Pardon?
Get out!
It is not too late to have a child now.
Hey.
I mean you are still healthy.
Catch that punk!
Oh, dear.
Why are there so many flowers here?
I tried to cut ties with someone,
and this is how he tries to make up.
I hope you forgive him.
The flowers are so pretty.
You speak such kind words.
Young Master Jang's mother
was also kind just like you.
Young Master Jang is kind too.
He is?
What makes you think he is kind?
When he talked about his mother,
I could feel the warmth
in his eyes.
What?
He spoke to you about his mother?
You two must be very close.
No, not yet.
He is the one who wishes to become close.
Last time,
he kept her busy for four hours.
Is that true?
We just had a chat.
So it really is you. The egret.
Young Master Jang can be blunt
due to his past scars.
But after he opens up to someone,
he is very kind and warm.
I hope you visit often.
Think of this place as your nest.
Feel free to fly in here and visit often.
I will.
Jin Mu is helping Jin Ho-gyeong
find her missing daughter?
It looks like he is
using that as an excuse
to frequently visit Jinyowon.
I guess Jin Mu wants Jinyowon on his side.
If Jin Mu gets his hands on Jinyowon,
he will become powerful enough
to fight against Songrim.
And…
if he no longer fears Songrim,
he and his men will reveal the ice stone
and show it to the world.
Someone on Jin Mu's side
is in possession of the ice stone.
The ice stone may seem like
it is made of ice,
but it also has the nature of fire,
water, and wind.
Just as a Choi family mage
did 200 years ago,
somebody is using the ice stone's power
to make the Soul Ejector.
This is the new batch of Soul Ejectors
made by the Queen.
It is not the power of the ice stone
that is evil.
It is the Soul Ejector
that is being used for evil deeds.
The kind of power
that is not granted to humans
but would be coveted by anyone
if available.
The power to leave the body
you no longer wish to live in
and move to a new one.
From an old body to a new one,
an ugly body to a beautiful one.
The power to stop death
and live for eternity.
He is a young, healthy,
and beautiful young man.
He has
already been selected to be my successor.
This is where I would like to move into.
Master.
What is the new spell
you promised to show me?
It is the alchemy of souls.
The alchemy of souls?
I still have many more things to achieve.
But this body is old
and facing death due to sickness.
Which is why…
I need your body.
What?
Let us begin the alchemy of souls.
Master, I do not wish to switch bodies.
If I enter your body, I will die soon.
But your body will still be alive.
Please help me.
Help me live.
Help! Help me!
Master!
Master.
My body…
Give me back my body.
Please. I do not wish to die.
Master! Give me back my body!
Master! I want my body back!
Master!
Once again, the soul of
another valuable mage has been saved
by the alchemy of souls.
As long as
we possess the power of the ice stone,
our souls will be able to live forever
instead of dying in this body.
The great power of the ice stone
is currently classified as sorcery,
which is why we have no choice
but to lie low like this.
But sooner or later, there will come a day
when our power grows strong enough for us
to show everyone that we were right
and that what we wish for is inevitable.
When that day comes,
everyone here
will overcome death
and be given eternal life.
Did you witness everything?
Yes.
Your job will be to bring someone here.
Jin Ho-gyeong is going to be your mother,
and I want you to win over her heart.
Then bring her to this place.
Can you do that?
Yes.
You found an adequate match.
If we manage to bring Jin Ho-gyeong here,
it will become easier for us
to reveal the ice stone to the world.
My love, why are you still up?
Jin Mu's power and influence
might be stronger
and more widespread than we think.
The King's Star must have appeared to deal
with the chaos brought by the ice stone.
Are you talking about Uk?
Master Seo Gyeong, who stopped the chaos
brought by the ice stone 200 years ago,
was also born with the energy
of the King's Star.
That King's Star
was created through sorcery.
You cannot compare that
to Master Seo Gyeong.
They are different.
I did not say they were the same.
That is why I am curious.
I am curious to see if this new star
will slowly fade away
or start shining brightly.
Win!
- Nice.
- Great job.
I knew you would win.
I know you use Tansu.
The Crown Prince was unaware,
which is why it worked.
But you used Tansu with water
from a puddle everyone can see.
It was not hard to block.
Win!
- You did great!
- Amazing!
There are only three toads left?
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
Does that mean he has been
fighting nonstop for the past seven days?
It means he continuously lost.
I thought he would stop if he kept losing.
But I guess
he will keep fighting for this.
You were right, Your Royal Highness.
His swordsmanship and spells are weak.
But he keeps fighting
only because he is persistent.
I know it is just a duel, but he has been
fighting Jeongjingak mages every day.
So I bet he is exhausted.
I am sure you will win,
Your Royal Highness.
Even I did not get a chance
to fight with Jeongjingak mages.
But I am letting Jang Uk do that
at the expense of my own gold toads.
Did I get fooled by Filthy Mu-deok?
Fight and perish, Jang Uk.
All the pain that does not kill you
will only make you stronger.
- Uk!
- You must be here for your young master.
Uk may be losing, but he is improving.
Do not go.
Do not go to your room and just stay here.
Goodness, look at your shoes.
They are drenched.
You are injured.
There is a commotion in the capital.
Some assassins attacked him last night.
- Do not kill him!
- Kill him.
- He is a soul shifter.
- Come on out!
- I will.
- Jang Uk.
I do not think it is right to let a mage
who has barged in here leave so easily.
Once they run wild,
there is no turning back.
They will no longer be humans,
but monsters.
We can also protect
the monsters from this world.
Subtitle translation by: Ja-won Lee